NinjaCatCastle working directory!

****BENCHMARK 2 NOTES****
//Mike 4/3/2015 4:38PM
PLEASE READ ALL OF THIS!
ok so guys I'm going to say some things about the second benchmark so we're all on the same page
it is due Monday the 13th. Box2D is the most important part of the assignment, and is probably the hardest part. 
I read some of the documentation and went through the testbed application that Box2D came with. 
So, now, since Dan is almost done with the sprites we're using for benchmark 2, 
Ryota and Dan will be doing most of the work involving getting Box2D to work as I work on the gameplay.
Inside box2D there is a project that has the test bed you can look at and play with to get to know box2D.
The main place to start with getting Box2D to work in McKenna's code is b2World. 
World is where all the magical stuff happens that makes it all come together 
(b2World is essentially serves the same purpose McKenna's physics.cpp class did)
On top of that, you guys should all download Jesse's better side scrolling framework. We are NOT using it, HOWEVER, 
Jesse left a TON of comments suggesting where Box2D may be implemented into the original code base. 
Take those comments and use it to help you guys make the structure for the code base we're using.
IF YOU GUYS HAVE ANY PROBLEMS WITH THE LINKER OR INCLUDING FILES TELL ME. 
I figured out how to do this myself so we can spend as little time dealing with stupid problems.
If either of you guys have any questions or problems you wanna ask, ask me. 
If there was anything you did not understand please tell me, I'll try to explain it better.

ONE LAST IMPORTANT THING: TURN LINE NUMBERS ON IN VISUAL STUDIO! THEY'RE OFF BY DEFAULT!
TUTORIAL HERE: https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms165340.aspx

If you haven't downloaded Visual Studio 2013 yet, do that please! That is the version of Visual Studio
that we are using for this project.

THAT'S IT FOR NOW! Ganbarimashou！ᕙ(⇀‸↼‶)ᕗ